# Amin Atashkhayer

(206) 733-0906 | ☑ <u>amin.atashin@gmail.com</u> | <u>in linkedin.com/in/amin-atashkhayer-5343a7196</u>
Website: https://my-portfolio-tawny-three.vercel.app

## **SKILLS**

Software Dev: HTML, CSS, Java Script, React.js, Typescript, Redux, BootstrapNode.js, Express.js, My SQL, MongoDB,PHP,Laravel

**Systems:** Computer Architecture, Software System design, Networks

**Other:** Microsoft Excel, Word, Power point, Photoshop

#### **Sciences & Healthcare:**

Anatomical Science, Physics. Health Insurance & Hospital Mgt;Biopharmaceutical Industry,MRI,CTscan

#### **Data Analytics:**

Statistic, T-test, Anova-test, Hypothesis-test, chi-squaretest

#### **EDUCATION**

Masters in Computer Sciences, New York, Monroe College 2022(Est. Grad. 2023)

Full Stack Web Development Epicode School, Berlin, Germany (2022)

## **BS** in Radiology

Mazandaran University of Medical Science, Iran (2015)

#### PROFESSIONAL STATEMENT

Experienced Radiology Technologist (5+ years exp.) earning a Master's in Computer Sciences (Dec2023) looking for an internship in Software Engineering. Full stack web developer with strong knowledge in life sciences, mathematics and data analytics. Experienced in web design and databases. Proven success in solving complex problems. Good communication skills in multi-cultural environment and efficient in collaborative, fast-paced work environments.

**PROJECTS** - Stack Tech Projects available at: O github.com/aminatashin

- Designed 'Travel with Us' website to assist visitors to search hotels, restaurants, heritage sites and other facilities using React.js, Google maps and Authentication.
- Developed 'Seize the Moment' website to post, like, edit and delete pictures as virtual diary using React.js, MongoDB and Authentication.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Developer, Epicode School, Berlin, Germany

Jan 2022 – Aug 2022

Collaborated with team of developers to replicate various websites such as LinkedIn, Spotify, Netflix, Amazon prime movies using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Java Script, React.js and MongoDB. Replicated WhatsApp using Socket.io, React.js and MongoDB.

## Radiology Tech, Several Medical Facilities, Iran

Feb 2015 - Oct 2020

Practiced general radiology including taking X-rays to diagnose a patient's illness or injury. Experienced in oral and maxillofacial radiology such as OPG, PA, Cephalometric, CBCT, etc.

# Statistical Researcher, Rome, Italy

Sept 2021--Dec 2021

Leveraged statistics to analyze and document various research projects, including:

- Demographic transition of various population age groups based on two senariuos: medium fertility and zero migration variants.
- Risk assessment for COVID-19 transmission at household level in sub-Saharan Africa based on evidence from DHS secondary analysis of the Demographic and Health Surveys of 16 African countries implemented between 2015 and 2018.
- Demographic analysis of Brazil and Japan based on factors such as age, race, and sex, expressed statistically through various indicators such as employment, education, income, marriage rates, birth, and death rates, etc.